sanic Underground Ranger blue the
fastest thing alive
Sonic the Hedgehog Sonic Underground
Ranger green the green badass Manic the
Hedgehog Sonic Underground ranger pink
the pink menace Sonia the Hedgehog Sonic
Underground Ranger yellow the richest
man alive
tough love among Clara president Sonic
Underground Ranger red Knuckles the cool
the kid not Sonic Underground rangers
orange the with the big boobs man
dalorto Sonic Underground Ranger Brown
I'm not he's dead more Claude Sonic
Underground Ranger purple the queen of
Mobius Queen Aleena Sonic Underground
European the college spoon Claire own
own could Sonic Underground dark Ranger
red the overlord of darkness dr.
Robotnik on Robotnik's
[Music]
[Applause]